～♪
#23 Before the War
Kazakiri!
風斬(かざきり)ーっ！
風斬！　風斬！
Kazakiri...
komorebi no naka wo futari de aruiteta
We always walked together through the sunlight
Are you hurt?
（上条）
気がついたか？
itsumo waraiau koto ga atarimae no youni
Laughing close together was our everyday
Thank goodness you're all right.
良かった　無事だったか
No...
（風斬）ダメですよ
（上条）あっ…
Why did this all happen?
（風斬）
なんで
こんなことになってるんですか？
tomodachitte kotoba sono hi iitakute
I wanted to say we were friends that day
It's all my fault.
全部 私のせいなのに
どうして私だけ無傷なんですか？
Why am I the only one unharmed?
If I can't be with everyone, then why was I born?
みんなと一緒には いられないなら
なんで私は生まれたんですか？
zutto soba ni irareru to omotteta nani ga attemo
And I thought nothing could separate us
I'm just a monster that can only exist thanks to all the espers.
能力者の人たちの力で やっと
存在していられる化け物なのに
Even though she called me a friend...
せっかく
あの子に友達って言ってもらえて
itsudatte wakeatta kimochi wa ima koko ni
You've shared your thoughts with me as I did with mine
少しは
人間らしくなれたと思ったのに
Even though I thought I'd become a little more human...
I'm sick of it all!
もうイヤなんです！
Please punch me and end it all!
私を殴って
全部 終わりにしてください
ikitsuiteru kara anata wo shinjiru yo
So I will put my trust in you and your words
Why...
なんで… なんで そんな顔を…
Why are you smiling?
Because I'm relieved.
（上条）安心したからだ
（風斬）えっ？
aitai to negau nara watashi wa tsuyoku nareru yo
My desire to see you gives me strength
I don't know why I have this power in my right hand.
俺の右手に どうして
こんな力が宿ってんのかは知らない
But I'll cut this hand off before I use it to make any of my friends disappear.
だけど
自分の友達を消しちまうぐらいなら
こんな右手 ここで
ぶち切ったほうが まだマシだ
donna kurayami demo yamanai ame no mukou
Strength to survive any darkness or rain
Why...
（風斬）どうして…
（泣き声）
お前は みんなを守っただろう
You protected everyone.
You did your best to protect everyone.
みんなを守るために
努力したんだろう？
kono koe ga kaze ni nori inori ga todoku nara
If the wind will carry my voice, my wish
Isn't that the human you wanted to be?
それは お前の思い描いてる
人間とは違うのか？
Be proud and look forward.
（上条）
胸を張れよ　前を見ろ
You continued to fight and saved people you didn't even know.
顔も知らない人のために
戦い続けて―
ちゃんと
みんなを守り抜いたお前に―
anata wo torimodoseru sono toki made
I will pray until you find your way back to my side
There's no reason to be disappointed.
うつむいてる理由なんか
ひとつもねえんだ
（上条）
一応 手当てが必要な人がいないか
確かめてみよう
I guess we'll check if anyone needs treatment.
Once that's done, let's go home.
（上条）
それが終わったら 帰ろう
I don't know when you're going to disappear.
お前が
いつ消えちまうかも分からないし
But we'll have to meet up with Index before that.
それまでに インデックスとも
合流しとかないとな
Don't ask why.
（上条）
“なんで”とか言ってんじゃねえぞ
友達だからに決まってんだろう
It's because we're friends, of course.
Are you okay?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
だ… 大丈夫なの？
The things on your back looked almost like a Telesma's...
背中のあれは テレズマに
酷似していたけど 一体…
What on Earth...
Hey!
（美琴(みこと)）
こら！
結局 何が どうなったのよ？
What happened?
Those huge wing things disappeared.
あのでっかい羽も
なくなったみたいだけど
If you need help, I'll head over there.
（美琴）
何か手伝うことがあれば
そっち行くけど
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
今 お医者さんを呼んでくるから
I'm going to go call a doctor!
Hey, wait!
（美琴）
ねえ ちょっと！
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
ハァ…
Accelerator, I'd like to talk with you.
（男性）
アクセラレータ
お話がありますが よろしいですか
Do you have a moment?
Telepathy...
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
テレパシーか
僅かだが 計算能力も戻ってる
I regained a little of my calculation ability.
Indeed, I have multiple telepathic espers.
（男性）
そのとおり　複数の
テレパス系能力者を用意しています
What is it?
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
何の用だ？
I'd like to discuss this incident, along with the damage it has caused to Academy City.
（男性）
あなたが引き起こした一連の騒動
ならびに―
学園都市が被った損害についての
ご相談をと思いまして
Are you going to dice me up and use me for research?
俺をめった斬りにして
研究素材にでもすんのか？
That's one possibility, but...
（男性）それも道のひとつですが
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）ああ？
How about working with us?
（男性）
我々と
行動を共にする気はありませんか？
Is Academy City planning to start a war?
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
学園都市は
戦争でも始めるつもりか？
I cannot answer that.
（男性）
お答えできません
I see.
そうかい
俺が言うべきことは ひとつだけだ
I only have one thing to say:
Like hell.
ふざけんじゃねえよ
This is the greatest crisis Academy City has faced.
（男性）
学園都市は ここが正念場です
We wish to stand up to it, and would appreciate your assistance.
我々は これに あらがいたいし
あなたにも協力してほしい
仮に学園都市が完全に消えた場合
我々能力者に居場所はあるのか
If Academy City were to disappear, would there be a place for us espers?
また
そのほかの技術に関しても同様に
The same goes for our technology.
チッ… ひとつだけ教えろ
Just answer me one thing.
What is it?
（男性）
何でしょう？
Who planned this?
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
今回の首謀者の名前だ
I'm going to rip off the neck of the person who used this kid.
あのガキをこんなふうに
扱った人間の首を切り落とす
I don't mind, but it'd just be another scapegoat.
（男性）
かまいませんが
どうせスケープゴートですよ
I see.
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）なるほど
（男性）…で どうしますか？
So, what's your answer?
Do what you want.
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）好きにしろ
（男性）よい返事です
A good answer.
（男性）
どうぞ よろしく
Nice to meet you, newbie.
新入りさん
（銃声）
Terra?
（ｱｯｸｱ）
テッラか
（ﾃｯﾗ）
ええ そうですよ
左方のテッラです
Yes, indeed. This is Terra of the Left.
そちらは終わりましたか？
Are you done?
Vento has been defeated.
（ｱｯｸｱ）
ヴェントがやられた
今 回収して―
I have recovered her and ordered the squad outside Academy City to stand down.
学園都市外周部の別動部隊を
下げさせたところである
Well done.
（ﾃｯﾗ）
ご苦労さまです
What's our next move?
（ｱｯｸｱ）
次は どう出る？
I don't mind if you tell me to go take the target's head.
何なら 私が標的の首を
切り落としてきても かまわんが
（ﾃｯﾗ）
やめておきましょう
Let's not.
We should plan carefully how best to make Academy City fall after listening to the details.
そちらの詳しい話を聞いたうえで
どう学園都市を落とすか―
考え直したほうがよさそうです
Make Academy City fall...
学園都市を落とす …か
Do you have a problem with that?
（ﾃｯﾗ）
気に入りませんか？
I am not fond of trickery.
小細工は苦手だ
It is always easier to destroy targets head-on.
倒すべき敵は 真正面から
倒したほうが楽に決まっている
Don't you think they have any reuse value?
（ﾃｯﾗ）
どうにでも利用価値があるとは
思えませんか？
例えば あの堕天使とか
For example, that fallen angel.
I won't agree to thievery on the battlefield.
戦場での略奪行為には
賛同しかねるぞ
Well said, Mr. Knight.
（ﾃｯﾗ）
さすが
騎士さまは言うことが違います
I am not a knight.
騎士ではない
私は傭兵(ようへい)崩れのごろつきである
I am a useless former mercenary.
Whatever, just take Vento and get back here.
（ﾃｯﾗ）
まあ ともあれ ヴェントを連れて
さっさと引き返してくださいね
It's an order from Fiamma of the Right.
こいつは 右方のフィアンマからの
指示でもあります
Understood.
了解した
I wonder if Academy City is as vulnerable as you think?
果たして 学園都市は
貴様が思っているほど―
貧弱な存在なのかね？
左方のテッラ
Terra of the Left...
Good morning, Aleister.
（ｶｴﾙ医者）
おはよう アレイスター
I have a thing or two to tell you...
ひとつ 君に言っておくべきことが
あるんだけどね
What is it?
（ｱﾚｲｽﾀｰ）
何だ？
Please don't toy with my patients.
（ｶｴﾙ医者）
僕の患者をおもちゃにするのは
やめてもらいたいんだ
フフッ…
聞かなかったら どうする？
And if I don't listen to you?
They are my patients, and I am a doctor.
あの子たちは 僕の患者なんだ
そして 僕は医者なんだ
分かるだろう？
Do you understand?
You should, being a patient I once saved, yourself.
（ｶｴﾙ医者）
かつて 僕に命を救われた君ならば
後悔してるのか？
Are you regretting it?
Are you seriously asking?
（ｶｴﾙ医者）
本気で尋ねてるのかい？
I cannot stop.
私は止まれない
もう その段階は過ぎている
That stage has already passed.
I bid you farewell.
お別れだ　優しい優しい私の敵
My kind, kind enemy.
（男子生徒）メシだ！
（男子生徒）購買へ急げ！
Lunch time!
Let's go!
Yakisoba bread, here I come!
（女子生徒）
今度こそ あの焼きそばパンを！
Hey!
（小萌(こもえ)）
こら！
廊下を走っちゃダメなのですよ！
Don't run in the hallway!
（上条）フフッ…
（姫神(ひめがみ)）ムムッ…
（上条）うん？
（姫神）なんだか今日は珍しい
What a coincidence.
That sure looks good.
また
うまそうなのを持ったヤツが来たな
I won't give you anything for free.
タダで分ける おかずはない
やるならトレード
If anything, I'll trade you.
I'm amazed you have the willpower to prepare a bento every day.
姫神って よく毎日毎日
弁当 用意する気力があるよな
あっ…
煮汁がご飯ゾーンに侵入してる
The juices are invading the rice zone.
You know, sometimes the juices make it taste good.
こ… この煮汁が染みてるのが
意外と うまかったりするんだぞ
負け惜しみ？
Sore loser?
No!
違う！　そんな顔するなら
この里芋を食べてみなさい
Have a potato; don't make that face.
うん　悪くはないかも
It's not too bad...
A-Are you all right, Himegami?
だ… 大丈夫か？　姫神
えっ 何だ？
さすったほうがいいのか？
What, should I rub your back?
Is it working?
（上条）どうだ？　姫神
（姫神）ンンッ…
Okay, stronger then?
（上条）そうか　もっと強くか？
（姫神）ンンッ…
（吹寄(ふきよせ)）何やってんだか
（上条）吹寄…
What are you doing?
Fukiyose...
Why do you always eat such bland bread?
お前 なんで いつも そんな
味気なさそうなパン食べてるわけ？
What? It's actually pretty good!
なによ！
ちゃんと おいしいわよ！
Power-Up Bread, with 12 nutrients to stimulate brain activity...
“脳を活性化させる12の栄養素が
入った能力上昇パン”？
（吹寄）
フン…
ハハハッ… 俺の里芋 食べるかね？
Would you like a potato?
By the way, I'm wearing a front-hook today.
言っておくけど
今日の私はフロントホックよ
（男子生徒Ａ）
マジかよ
Are you serious?
They're saying if the travel restrictions become too strict, our field trip may be canceled.
（男子生徒Ｂ）
街の入場制限 厳しくなると
社会見学なくなるかもって
I hope it doesn't affect Ichihanaransai.
（男子生徒Ｃ）
一端覧(いちはならん)祭にまで影響しねえだろうな
Oh right, they're saying we might skip midterms since the Anti-skill teachers are part of the defense preparations.
（女子生徒Ａ）
そうそう
警備員(アンチスキル)の先生たちが対策練るから
中間テストどころじゃ
なくなるってさ
Really?
（女子生徒Ｂ）
ホント？
A war, huh?
（吹寄）戦争か
（上条）うん？
That's troublesome.
まいってしまうわよね
だって 戦争が始まったら―
If a war starts, the prices of meat and vegetables will rise.
お肉とか野菜とかの値段が
上がっちゃうんでしょう？
あと お決まりの石油とかも
And petroleum, too.
Hey, Kamijou.
（吹寄）ねえ 上条
（上条）うん？
Why are you so quiet?
さっきから なに黙ってるわけ？
い… いや 何でも
N-No reason.
I was just thinking maybe we should eat hot pots before it's too late.
だったら 今のうちに鍋とか
食べておいたほうが得なのかな
So we don't regret it later, you know!
（上条）
あとになって 食べときゃ
よかったってことにならないように
Yeah, but...
あっ… そうだけど
Oh, you're having hot pot today?
（青髪ﾋﾟｱｽ）
あれ？
カミやん 今日 鍋にすんの？
I know a cheap sukiyaki place!
（土御門(つちみかど)）
にゃ～！　すき焼きだったら
安くて うまい店 知ってるぜ
What, you guys are eating out today?
（男子生徒Ｄ）
なんだ お前ら
今日 どっか行くわけ？
We can't let you hog a good restaurant.
（男子生徒Ｅ）
うまい店の独り占めとは
許せませんなぁ
（男子生徒）
つうか
なんで いきなり また鍋なわけ？
Why a hot pot so suddenly, anyway?
Majority vote!
（男子生徒）多数決 多数決！
（上条）あれ？
Uh... when did this turn into a class dinner trip?
いつの間に クラスみんなで
晩ご飯を食べに行く話に…
（上条）
うん？　ふ… 吹寄さん？
Fukiyose-san?
…たく
Sheesh...
フン…
Fukiyose forehead deluxe?!
吹寄おでこデラックス！
Tonight's
Dinner
I'll take care of things, so hurry up and vote!
さあ この私が面倒みてやるから
さっさと清き１票を入れなさい！
Tsukuyomi-sensei, I heard you housed another run-away kid.
（黄泉川(よみかわ)）
月詠(つくよみ)先生　また新しい家出少女を
保護したって言ってたじゃん
I was a little lonely after Himegami-chan went to the school dorms,
姫神ちゃんが学校の寮に入ってから
ちょっと寂しかったんですけど
but I'm fine now that Musujime-chan is here.
結標(むすじめ)ちゃんが来たから
もう大丈夫なのですよ
The kid at my house left already.
うちの居候は 薄情にも
さっさと出ていったじゃんよ
（生徒たち）おお～！
（小萌）ウワッ！　なっ！
It's decided!
（吹寄）
決定！　今夜は みんなで
すき焼きに決定しました！
We're going to a sukiyaki restaurant tonight!
アア…
ちょっと収拾つけてくるのですよ
I'm going to put things in order!
（戸の開く音）
（小萌）こら！
Hey!
What are you all shouting about?!
何を騒いでるんですか！
Oh, Komoe-sensei!
フフッ… いいなぁ
How nice, they get to spend their time just doing stupid things.
バカみたいなこと
ばかりで
（吹寄）
それでは…
Now, then...
Let's eat!
（生徒たち）
いただきま～す！
（小萌）
ハァ… 保護者の皆さまから―
Parents are starting to demand that their children come home due to the impending danger of war in Academy City...
“もし戦争が起きたら
学園都市は危ないから―”
“子供を返して”っていう
お問い合わせが増えているのですよ
Really? I hadn't heard that.
えっ？
そんな話になってんですか？
上条　なんで貴様は そんなに
モタモタと卵を溶いてるわけ？
Kamijou!
What the hell is taking you so long with that egg?
（上条）えっ？
（吹寄）ああ もう イライラする！
Gah, you're irritating!
Give that here!
（吹寄）ちょっと貸しなさい！
（上条）あっ… 仕切り屋？
You're going to feed me?!
Kami-yan.
（青髪ﾋﾟｱｽ）カミやん
（上条）うん？
メニューを見るかぎりやと
まだ値段は変わっとらんようやね
It doesn't seem like the prices have changed much yet, judging from the menu.
I-I guess...
Here.
（吹寄）はい！
（上条）あっ… サンキュー
Thank you.
Their next shipping is probably going to be pricier though.
あっ でも
仕入れの段階では上がってるかもな
つまり 今のうちに
食っとけっちゅうことやんな？
So basically, now's the time to strike!
Yoink!
そ～れ！
Hey, don't take just the meat!
あっ！
てめえ 肉ばっか取りやがって！
Touma!
当麻(とうま)　お肉 おかわり！
I want more meat!
But... I haven't had a single piece yet...
えっ？　お前… 俺は まだ
ひと口も食べてないっていうのに
War, huh...?
戦争か… なんとかしないとな
Guess I'll need to do something.
（土御門）カミやん
（上条）うん？
Kami-yan.
You're wrong if you think this war is all your fault.
（土御門）
これから起こる戦争が―
全部 自分のせいだって
思ってんなら 大間違いだぞ
You've done nothing but protect everyone around you.
お前は これまで
周りの連中を守ってきたんだ
I guess so...
そうか …な
This war is happening because someone behind the scenes screwed up.
戦争が起こったのは
裏方が しくじったからだ
（土御門）始まるぞ
（上条）ああ
It's starting.
Yeah.
（土御門）
戦いの規模が変わる
The scale of the battles is changing.
At this rate, the situations will become harder and harder to deal with.
今のままで これからの局面を
くぐり抜けるのは難しいだろう
そうだな　むしろ―
You're right...
Actually, I think it's a miracle that I've gotten this far.
今まで なんとかできてたほうが
奇跡的だったんだ
I've been too naive.
今まで 俺は甘えていたんだ
I've let everyone else deal with the other world.
自分の知らない世界のことを
全部 他人に任せてた
But I can't do that anymore.
でも これからは それじゃダメだ
I have to take my own steps into the new world.
俺は
今まで見てこなかった新しい世界に
足を踏み入れなくちゃ
いけないんだよ
Tsuchimikado, I've made up my mind.
（上条）
土御門　俺は決めた
カミやん…
Kami-yan...
Yes, I'm...
そう　俺は…
I'm going to start studying English!
俺は これから英語を勉強する
（土御門）え～っ？
（上条）今 日常会話の―
I'm on "Daily Conversations Level 3" right now...
レベル３に挑戦してんだけど
やっぱり 英語って難しいな
Seriously, though, English is tough.
Why are you studying English?
なぜ この局面で英語…
Up until now, I've relied on others using Japanese.
今までは みんな
日本語で合わせてくれてたけど
I shouldn't be too dependent on that, though!
こっちが それに甘え続けるのは
ダメなんだよ
That's why, in conclusion...
つまり 結論を言うとだな…
Wh-Why?
（上条）
な… なんで？
（ブザー）
（ｱﾅｳﾝｽ）演習ナンバー42
Exercise Number 42, begin.
開始します
Exercise Number 43, begin.
（ｱﾅｳﾝｽ）
演習ナンバー43　開始します
What do you want, disguise-boy?
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
何の用だ？　変装野郎
I was trying to conceal my presence,
（海原(うなばら)）
自分なりに気配ってやつを
断ってみたんですけどね
but it seems I need more practice.
やはり
まだまだ修行不足のようです
海原光貴(みつき) …だったか？
Unabara Mitsuki, was it?
Both my face and name are fake, though.
顔も名前もニセモノですけどね
Have you decided on a weapon yet?
（海原）
武器のほうは決まりましたか？
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
しっくり来る物(もん)はねえな
None of these feel right.
I doubt I'd find one even if I checked every gun in the world.
世界中の銃を集めても
見つかんねえかもな
能力使用を前提とした
装備リストを固めてみては？
How about putting together a list of equipment you can use with your power?
You don't get it, do you?
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
知ったような口利くんじゃねえよ
こいつは頼りにならねえ
I can't rely on this thing.
GROUP's technical team reports that they extended its usage up to 30 minutes.
グループの技術部の報告では―
能力使用時間が
30分に延長したという話ですが
GROUP, eh?
“グループ”ね
Do you have issues with how the electrode is tuned?
（海原）
電極のチューンに何か不満が？
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
フン… 30分だろうが ３日だろうが
It doesn't matter if it's 30 minutes or 3 days.
Any irregularities will make this thing useless.
イレギュラーが起きれば
それまでだ
If I can't fight when it breaks down, then I'm as good as dead.
“故障したから戦えません”じゃ
生き残れねえだろうが
Is that all?
要件は それだけか？
統括理事会から 我々グループに
仕事のオーダーが入りました
GROUP has received orders from the Board of Directors.
Academy City is fortifying its defenses against the Roman Catholic Church.
（海原）
学園都市は 対ローマ正教用の
布陣を固めているところですが
As a result, the defense within the city has thinned, though.
そのために内側への防御が
手薄になりつつあるのも事実です
Our job is to take care of a particular force that plans to take advantage of that gap in security.
今回は その隙を突いてくる勢力の
ひとつを一掃します
フフッ… 木原(きはら)のくそ野郎の
穴埋めをやらされるって話だったが
I was told that I'd make up for what Kihara did,
まさか そんな くだらねえ仕事を
回されるとはな
but I didn't think I'd have to do crap like this.
As much as you may not like it, you brought this upon yourself.
自分に当たられましても…
勝手に落ちてきたのは
あなたですし
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
ンッ！　いいか？　小僧
ひとつだけ教えてやる
Listen up, kid.
There's one thing you need to understand.
Human life is a fragile thing.
人間の命ってのは貧弱だ
俺が指先で触れた程度で
壊れちまうぐらいにな
So weak that I can destroy it with a touch of my finger.
So watch what you say.
だから 少しは気を遣え
If you don't, I might break something I shouldn't.
じゃねえと
要らねえもんまで砕いちまいそうだ
I'll keep that in mind.
（海原）気をつけましょう
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）チッ…
（海原）続けてもよろしいですか？
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）勝手にしろ
May I continue?
Whatever.
Our target is Skillout.
（海原）
標的となる対象はスキルアウト
You may know them better than I do.
あなたのほうが
詳しいかもしれませんね
ああ　レベル０たちが
集まってる武装集団だな？
They're an armed group of Level 0's, right?
Yes.
ええ　現在 連中は―
It would seem that they're constructing some "toys" for themselves.
おもちゃを作っているようです
"Toys"?
おもちゃ？
They're drilling into wood and stuffing them with explosives as makeshift rockets.
（海原）
木材をくり抜いて
中に爆薬を詰めたロケット砲です
Something like pole fire arrows from the Edo period.
江戸(えど)時代に試作された
棒火矢といったところでしょうか
Over the past few days, they've been at work in various places.
彼らは この数日間の間に
あちこちで工作を行っています
Dragging abandoned bikes near emergency routes,
（海原）
災害時の誘導経路のそばに
放置自転車を移動させたり
clogging drains around VIP passageways with garbage.
ＶＩＰ施設周辺の排水溝に
ゴミを詰めて 塞いだりと―
保安上の問題として―
Small things that aren't really considered security concerns, but...
取り上げるようなものでは
ありませんが
So GROUP's job is to clean up after brats making a mess?
グループってのは―
ガキのいたずらの後始末まで
請け負ってんのか
（海原）
ですが 既に２万件以上
The problem is, there have been over 20,000 reported cases already.
So now, during a Code Orange or Red, they'll be passed off as an error.
オレンジやレッドの警報時には―
エラーとして
検出されてしまうんです
So that's why they're making those pole fire arrows?
そのための棒火矢だってのか？
大量のエラー報告によって
サーバーがダウンしてしまえば―
If the sheer number of errors knocks out the communications server,
スキルアウトたちが暴れても
警備員(アンチスキル)は やって来ない
Skillout will be free to run wild without Anti-skill being notified.
Why don't you just turn off the alert system, then?
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
じゃ
警報を解除すりゃいいんだろう？
We would if we weren't at war.
（海原）
今が戦争中でなければね
Enemies both inside and out, huh...
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
内も外も敵だらけ …か
学園都市ってのは―
It seems Academy City has made a hell of a lot of enemies.
よほど多くの人間から
恨まれてるみてえだな
And it is our job to deal with them.
そういう人々をなんとかするのが
我々の仕事です
ターゲットの名前は 駒場利徳(こまば りとく)
Our target's name is Komaba Ritoku.
He is the leader and the brains of Skillout.
現在のスキルアウトを
束ねるリーダーで
頭脳でもあります
If we can take care of him fast enough, we'll be able to counter Skillout's plans.
彼を速やかに処分することで―
スキルアウト側の計画を
未然に防ぎます
So why am I in a garbage truck?
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
なんでゴミ収集車なんだよ？
It's the most convenient, seeing as we can take care of corpses easily, too.
（海原）
何かと便利なんですよ
死体の処分などもありますから
So the "garbage" this truck collects is corpses, huh?
くそ野郎の死体をあさる収集車か
笑えねえ話だ
That's no laughing matter.
As instructed, I'll pick you up in 20 minutes.
（海原）
指示どおり 20分後に回収に来ます
お気をつけて
Be careful.
フゥ… 勝っても負けても
あれに乗るわけか
So I'll be back in that truck whether I win or lose.
Either as I am or as a corpse...
生身か死体かは さておいてな
So this is designed to keep security robots out.
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
警備ロボット対策に―
Cheap tricks to avoid satellite observation?
人工衛星の監視を
逃(のが)れるための小細工か
What a nostalgic atmosphere.
懐かしい空気だ
土御門か
Tsuchimikado?
（土御門）
そろそろ 初陣だと思ってな
お前に忠告しておくことがある
Your first job's about to start, right?
I figured I'd give you a word of advice.
Advice?
忠告と来たか
…で 内容は何だよ？　先輩
And what might that be, Senpai?
Don't trust us.
（土御門）俺たちのことを信じるな
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）ああ？
Huh?
Every one of us would be in trouble if our existence became known to the public.
（土御門）
俺たち全員―
その存在が表に出ただけで
問題になるような連中ばかりだ
そういう人間ばかりを選んで
作られたグループにゴールはない
There can be no unity amongst a group formed like that.
Were you hoping I'd be grateful you told me that?
この俺が ご褒美を
期待してるとでも言いてえのか？
If you follow the rules the Board of Directors has laid out, then there's no way to outdo them.
（土御門）
統括理事会が決めたルールに
従ってるだけじゃ―
ヤツらは出し抜けないって話だ
You need to think about how you're going to win in this situation.
その上で
勝つには どうしたらいいか
そいつを認識しておけよ
Both you and I have something to protect.
俺も お前も
守るべきものを持ってんだからな
Is that all you wanted?
要件は それだけか？
Finish it quickly.
（土御門）
早いところ 終わらせて帰ってこい
Musujime's probably starting her job right about now.
結標のほうも そっちで
そろそろ仕事を始めるだろうしな
Her job?
仕事だと？
Nobody told me this was going to be a competition.
競争とは聞いてねえんだけどな
She's not after the members, she's after the money.
（土御門）
あいつが狙っているのは
人じゃない　金だ
So she's still useful.
つうか
あいつ まだ使い物になったんか
She's the same as you.
（土御門）
お前と同じだよ　補強してる
You both have assistance.
Oh? Fine by me.
そうかい　そりゃ結構
Well, then...
そんじゃ まあ 始めるとしますか
I guess I'll get started.
I'll finish cleaning this up in 10 minutes.
お片づけだ　10分で終わらせてやる
（男性たち）
オリャー！
That makes nine.
（結標）
これで９か所
歯応えが足りないわね
This just isn't enough for me.
（駒場）
少しは加減してほしいものだな
能力者
I'd appreciate it if you'd stop that, esper.
フン… 駒場利徳
Komaba Ritoku.
Who would've thought I'd run into the target first?
あら まあ　こちらが先に
ターゲットとぶつかってしまったわ
～♪
Next Episode
GROUP enters intense combat with the Level 0s.
（上条）
激突するグループと無能力者たち
Misaka Misuzu gets dragged in the mess.
御坂美鈴(みさか みすず)を巻き込み 大混乱に
And Accelerator and I meet again.
俺とアクセラレータは再び…
次回 「武装集団(スキルアウト)」
Next time: "Skillout."
When science and magic cross paths, this epic will begin!
科学と魔術が交差するとき
物語は始まる